Meet Mr. Ong Chong Tun Peng from China.
118 years 3 months and 28 days of age.
Longest living person in the history of Mankind.
I'll break this Chinese guy's record.
Only 16 years to go.
Yo!
But there's a problem - What?
It is impossible to live so long
With this boring, unenthusiastic, old man.
You know, he inhales so much air...
...that sometimes I wonder whether there will be enough left for me.
Look, I am a 75-year-old man.
I've accepted my old age.
That's why, I am sending you to an Old Age Home!
Old Age Home.
I am the father.
And I want to send my son to the Old Age Home.
Why is it so difficult to understand...
Hello...
Tell me what I've to do.
Write a love-letter.
To your beloved wife.
Yo... You want me to write a love letter?
Who else will write a love letter to your wife?
"Dear Chandrika..."
"My entire existence is nestled..."
"...in the sacchariferous reminiscences of our pulchritudinous marital life."
What's this? Latin?
How many lives will you claim...
...in your quest for a long life?
If your son grows up to be a rascal...
...then forget him.
Just remember his childhood.
Just the childhood.
And if you try to interfere...
...then I will drag you to court!
Yo!
"Oh Chandrika."
"A father who thinks about sending his own son to an old age home..."
"... must be such a mother...!!!